Imogen Cunningham
Archives of American Art, Smithsonian Institution
Chappell, Walter: Dec 01, 1972* (recommendation by Cunningham to Guggenheim Foundation); also see Eastman: George Eastman House
Cheney, Hal: Sep 23, 1972*
Chilberg, Mabel: Dec 22, 1966; Aug 03, 1970*; Aug 08, 1970
Chin, Bobtoy: see Bobtoy
Chinn, Benjamin: undated
Chipp, Herschel: May 05, 1967
Christian Science Monitor: May 29, 1959; Jun 01, 1959; Jun 11, 1959*; Aug 10, 1959; Aug 14, 1959*
Christy, George: May 28, 1974; Jul 30, 1974*
Ciabattari, Jane: see Aphra
Cincinnati Art Museum: Mar 07, 1960
Citizens' Vigilance Committee: Aug 14, 1962; Sep 08, 1962* (letter to Board of Supervisors, San Francisco); Sep 08, 1962* (letter to Recreation and Park Commission, San Francisco)
Clayden, Marian: Dec 22, 1974*; May 12, 1976
Cleaver, Virginia: Jul 08, 1974*
Clergue, Lucien: Oct 31, 1972 (6 photographs of Cunningham by Clergue); Apr 04, 1973*; Sep 07, 1973*; Jan 15, 1974*; mentioned in letter dated Feb 01, 1974; Feb 16, 1974
Close-Up: see Polaroid Corporation
Coates, L. D.: Jan 15, 1968
Coburn, Alvin Langdon: Apr 14, 1913; Feb 19, 1953*; Jun 02, 1960; [Jan] 1964; Sep 10, 1964
Coe, Gertrude: Mar 20, 1960; Feb 21, 1966; Feb 28, 1966*; Dec 10, 1966; May 12, 1967*
Coe, Lucy Campbell: Jun 07, [1966]; Sep 13, 1966*; Dec 11, 1966*; Dec 23, 1966; May 30, 1967*; Jun 19, 1967*; Jun 18, 1973 (including a photograph of Elsa Walsh by Cunningham)
Coelen, Leslie: Mar 13, 1971*
Cohan, Mr.: Apr 16, 1965*
Coke, Van Deren: Feb 27, 1969* (including resume)
Cole, Howard: Mar 09, 1967; Mar 17, 1967*; Mar 17, 1967*; May 26, 1967; May 29, 1967*; Jul 06, 1967; Aug 30, 1973
College of Marin: Nov 06, 1967; Nov 11, 1967*; Jan 02, 1968; Jan 05, 1968*; Jan 19, 1968*
Colum, Padraic: Apr 20, 1956*
Colwell, Larry: Dec 03, 1958; Jun 01, 1959*; Apr 12, 1960; Jan 09, 1961*; Jan 18, 1961; Feb 15, 1961*; Apr 20, 1961*; May 02, 1961; Aug 25, 1961; Dec 08, 1964; Feb 14, 1965*; Oct 13, 1965*; Sep 09, 1966; Sep 23, 1966; Oct 02, 1966*; Nov 09, 1966; Dec 21, 1966*; Jan 17, 1967; May 02, 1967*; May 02, 1968*; Nov 10, 1968; Dec 29, 1969*
Comer, Deirdre and Tony: undated (2); Nov 17, 1960*; Feb 07, 1966*; Apr 29, 1969*
Comer, Molly and Fred: undated (2; including a photograph of their view of the river); Jan 29, 1944 (2); Dec 1949 (including 2 photographs of their house); Jun 02, 1951*; Jan 24, 1952*; Jul 18, 1952*; Aug 04, 1952; Dec 02, 1952*; Feb 13, 1953*; Nov 11, 1953*; Nov 27, 1953; Nov 18, 1954; Jan 05, 1955; Nov 19, 1955
Conde Nast Publications, Ltd.: May 12, 1961
Connelly & Associates: Jul 16, 1964*
Connor, Linda: Dec 15, 1973 (including photograph by Connor)
Conrad, Barnaby: Mar 19, 1976
Constantine, Mildred: Oct 13, 1974*
Cook: Thomas Cook & Son: Jan 21, 1960 (re voyage on the BERLIN)
Cooper, Thomas: Sep 20, 1970; Sep 20, 1970*; Nov 09, 1971; Nov 12, 1971*; Nov 16, 1972; Dec 03, 1972*; Sep 20, 1973; Feb 26, 1975
Cooper Union for the Advancement of Science and Art: Jul 16, 1956
Corbett, A.: Jun 04, 1970
Costello, Allison: undated
Couchman, Bea: Feb 26, [1967]; Jan 05, 1968; Jan 10, 1968*; Jan 26, 1970*; Aug 18, 1970*; May 27, 1971; Aug 06, [1973]
Cowll, Sidney: Mar 24, 1974*
Cranbrook Academy of Art: Apr 22, 1976
Crane, Barbara: Feb 11, 1971; Jun 04, 1971*; Nov 24, 1971* (letter of recommendation); Nov 27, 1971* (letter of recommendation); [Apr 1973]*; May 26, 1973
Craven, George and Rachel: Mar 20, 1960; Oct 12, 1960*; Oct 21, 1960; Nov 16, 1960*; Apr 20, 1962*; Apr 26, 1962; [Dec 1963]; Mar 13, 1964*; Apr 09, 1964*; Jun 30, 1964*; Oct 03, 1964; Mar 07, 1966; Mar 10, 1966*; Mar 24, 1966*; Mar 25, 1966; May 02, 1966; May 04, 1966*; Oct 05, 1966*; Dec 21, 1969; Sep 07, 1972 (booklet “The Group f/64 Controversy" by Craven enclosed in letter to Cunningham from University of California at Berkeley)
Crawford & Conover, Inc.: Aug 06, 1965
Crawford, Earl: Feb 17, 1975; Mar 24, 1975*
Creative and Extraordinary Person Project: Sep 01, 1974
Creative Camera: Feb 10, 1971; Jun 16, 1971; Jun 29, 1971*; Jul 08, 1971*
Crispino, Miss: Jul 06, 1968*
Crockett, Candace: Feb 11, 1974; Feb 17, 1974*
Crouch, Steve: Jan 25, 1960*; Jun 06, 1968; Jun 18, 1968*
Crowder, Katherine Kerr: Jun 21, 1965; Jun 27, 1965*
Crowell: Thomas Y. Crowell Company: Feb 12, 1962; Feb 26, 1962; Mar 02, 1962; Mar 06, 1962
Crowninshield, Frank: May 09, 1935; Jun 10, 1935*; Jun 13, 1935
Cunningham, Andy: Jan 08, 1967
Cunningham, Augusta: May 18, 1976
Cunningham: Friends of Imogen Cunningham: Apr 12, 1979; Apr 12, 1980; Apr 12, 1981; Apr 12, 1982; Apr 12, 1983
Cunningham: Imogen Cunningham Trust: Mar 01, 1976; also see Morrison & Foerster; also see entry under Financial Material
Cunningham, John: May 24, 1974*
Cunningham, June and Alan: Jun 27, 1976
Cunningham, Lynn: Jan 07, 1972; Feb 09, 1972*; Aug 11, 1972*; May 02, 1973; May 16, 1973*
Cunningham?, Min: 1910*
Cunningham, Pearl: 1909 (3)*; 1910 (6, including a photograph of a woman drinking beer while holding a cigarette)
Cunningham Press: Jan 12, 1974*
Cunningham, Roger and Doris: Dec 25, 1967 (including photo Christmas card); Feb 15, 1968; Jul 15, 1968*; Aug 08, 1968; Dec 06, 1968; Dec 07, 1968 (including photo Christmas card); Apr 27, 1969*; May 11, 1969; Dec 13, 1969 (including photo Christmas card); Feb 25, 1970; Mar 03, 1970*; May 21, 1970; May 27, 1970 (including obituary for Nellie Cunningham); Jun 11, 1970; Apr 16, 1971*; Jan 11, 1972; [Apr 29, 1974]; May 08, 1974*; May 16, 1974; May 23, 1974*; Mar 31, 1975*; Apr 21, 1976*; Apr 27, 1976; Nov 30, 1979; Nov 30, 1979
Cunningham, Mr. and Mrs. T. N.: Mar 31, 1975*
Cushing, Nancy: undated; Jun 30, 1976 (letter of condolence to Gryffyd Partridge)
Dadd, Mary: see McEwan, Mary
Dafoe, Dottie and Leslie: Apr 07, 1970; Nov 12, 1970*; Nov 12, 1970*; Dec 11, 1973
Dahl, Arthur L.: Nov 20, 1970*
Daily Express: Jul 07, 1960
Dallas Museum for Contemporary Arts: Dec 11, 1967
Daniel, Edna: Aug 24, 1961; Feb 20, 1963; Feb 26, 1969*; also see California: University of California at Berkeley
Danieli, Fidel: Aug 09, 1974; Oct 28, 1974*
Dater, Judy: Nov 27, 1971* (letter of recommendation); July 1973; Dec 04, 1974* (letter of recommendation); Oct 28, 1979
Daveney, Paula: Sep 07, 1943*; Feb 03, 1948; Jul 10, 1956 (letter from Berta Hader); Mar 02, 1971*; Oct 19, 1973*; Mar 11, 1974*; Sep 14, 1974*; Mar 10, 1975 (filing of Daveney's will); see Personal business records
David: Peter M. David Gallery: Nov 18, 1974; Nov 22, 1974*
Davidos, Rajan and Kimiko: Jan 05, 1969*; Apr 09, 1969; Apr 13, 1969*; also see Photographs
Davies, Louise: undated (3); Mar 04, 1971*; May 16, 1973*
Davies, Ralph: Sep 20, 1970*
Davis, Phil: May 20, 1974; May 25, 1974*; Jun 18, 1974; Aug 20, 1974*
DAY AT NIGHT (television program): Apr 25, 1974; May 03, 1974*
Dearborn, Betty: Apr 10, 1967; Jun 19, 1967*
Dearborn-Massar: see Massar, Phyllis
Dearborn Stove Company: Apr 21, 1965*
DeCordova and Dana Museum and Park: Nov 15, 1961; Mar 07, 1968*
DeGoff, Sidney: Oct 19, 1974*
Deitch, Donna: Jan 07, 1972; Jan 19, 1972*; Feb 24, 1975*; Mar 23, 1976; Apr 01, 1976*
Denny, Grace: Feb 06, 1967; May 06, 1967; Aug 24, 1967
Desmarais, Charles: Oct 11, 1974
Detroit Free Press: Sep 15, 1965; Sep 21, 1965; Oct 25, 1965
Deutsch, Barbara: Feb 18, 1974
De Young Museum: Nov 21, 1970 (letter from Janet Partridge)
De Young Museum Society: Jun 24, 1970
Dhaemers, Mrs.: Mar 04, 1966*
Diablo Valley College: Aug 15, 1972; Nov 15, 1972
Diamond, Martin: Oct 02, 1974; Feb 24, 1975*
Dickinson-Chetham, Helen: Dec 10, 1960*; Aug 28, 1962 (letter to Dorothy MacDonald); Jun 03, 1963
Dill, Robert: Jul 22, 1970; Aug 03, 1970*; Sep 19, 1973
Dinsdale, Elizabeth: Sep 02, 1968; also see Cunningham, Roger
Dixon, Constance (daughter of Maynard Dixon): Jun 30, 1976 (letter of condolence to Gryffyd Partridge)
Dixon, Edith: Nov 1946 (re death of Maynard Dixon)
Dmitri, Ivan: see Photography in the Fine Arts
Dommeyer, Frederick C.: Oct 01, 1965; Jun 21, 1966
Doniach, Sarah: Mar 03, 1970; Mar 12, 1970*
Donnelley, Adelaide: [Mar 29, 1972]; Mar 29, 1972*; Jun 10, 1972*; Jun 28, 1972
Donoho, David: undated (2); Sep 30, 1963; Feb 15, 1965; Mar 01, 1966; Mar 03, 1966*; Dec 12, 1966; Jan 02, 1967; Jan 04, 1967*; Mar 08, 1967; Apr 03, 1967; Apr 11, 1967; May 11, 1967; May 17, 1967; May 24, 1967; May 30, 1967*; Jun 02, 1967; Jul 27, 1967; Aug 01, 1967; Aug 07, 1967; Sep 17, 1967; Sep 29, 1967*; Oct 07, 1967*; Nov 05, 1967; Jul 03, 1968; Jul 08, 1968*; Jul 11, 1968; Sep 27, 1968*; Sep 29, 1968; Oct 13, 1968; Nov 12, 1968; Dec 03, 1968; Dec 24, 1968; Mar 12, 1969*; Mar 16, 1969; May 20, 1970; Mar 23, 1971; Mar 27, 1971*; Apr 20, 1972*; May 21, 1974; Jun 05, 1975; Jun 29, 1975; also see San Jose State College
Dooley: Thomas A. Dooley Foundation, Inc.: see Chaney, Verne
Doubleday & Company, Inc.: Nov 12, 1970; Nov 26, 1970*
Dowling, Ed and Muriel Peterson: Jul 18, 1958*; Aug 29, 1965*
Doyle, Kathleen: undated
Dresden, Maud: May 31, 1910 (2) (a postcard with a photograph of Dresden and Cunningham; and a postcard with a photograph of Dresden and Omer Foisie)
Dreyfus, Emile: Sep 26, 1955 (including 2 photographs of “old fogies" playing card game)
Drummond, Katherine: Apr 20, 1961*; Oct 07, 1961; Dec 29, 1963*; Jan 27, 1964; Jan 03, 1967; Sep 22, 1968*
Duarte, Carlota: Apr 28, 1976
Ducasse, Mabel and Curt (Brown University): Sep 17, 1956; Dec 25, 1956; Jan 10, 1959*; Dec 07, 1960; Dec 14, 1960*; Dec 29, 1963*; Jan 10, 1964; Jan 20, 1964*; Feb 22, 1964*; Oct 07, 1964; [Jan 1965]; Feb 05, 1966; Feb 12, 1966; Feb 14, 1966*; Feb 26, 1966; Mar 01, 1966*; Mar 25, 1966; Apr 05, 1966*; Oct 16, 1966; Nov 10, 1966*; Dec 27, 1966; Apr 26, 1967*; Apr 29, 1967; May 23, 1967*; May 24, 1967; May 26, 1967*; Jun 07, 1967; Jun 08, 1967; Jun 18, 1967*; Jun 27, 1967; Aug 14, 1967*; Nov 26, 1967*; Dec 15, 1968*; Jan 06, 1969*; Dec 14, 1969; Dec 29, 1969*; Jan 08, 1970; Feb 02, 1970; Mar 08, 1970*; Mar 17, 1970; May 25, 1970; Jun 12, 1970*; mentioned in letter dated Sep 27, 1975
Dunham, Dorothea: Apr 08, [1976]
Duskin, Mr.: undated*
E., Charline: Feb 14, 1967*; Apr 04, 1968; Apr 10, 1968*; Mar 17, 1970
E., W.?: Jul 08, 1960
Eakins Press: Apr 30, 1976*
Eastman: George Eastman House: Jun 25, 1958; Nov 27, 1958*; Feb 05, 1959*; Apr 21, 1959; Jun 23, 1959; Jul 06, 1959*; Jul 16, 1959; Aug 10, 1959; Aug 18, 1959; Sep 04, 1959*; Nov 17, 1959*; Nov 23, 1959; Dec 20, 1959*; Jan 01, 1960*; Feb 12, 1960*; May 12, 1960; Jul 15, 1960; Sep 21, 1960; Oct 14, 1960; Nov 02, 1960; Dec 23, 1960; Dec 30, 1960; Mar 21, 1961*; Apr 06, 1961*; Apr 03, 1962; May 18, 1962*; May 24, 1962; Jun 05, 1962*; Jul 10, 1962; Aug 03, 1962; Nov 28, 1962*; Jan 11, 1963; Jan 17, 1963*; Nov 20, 1963*; [Dec 1963]; Apr 25, 1964*; Jun 08, 1964*; Jul 08, 1964; Jul 28, 1965*; Jun 29, 1967*; Apr 04, 1968*; Aug 14, 1969*; Sep 17, 1969*; Sep 30, 1969; Jul 07, 1970*; Aug 25, 1970; Sep 04, 1970*; Sep 21, 1970; Sep 28, 1970*; Oct 08, 1970; Oct 16, 1970*; Oct 20, 1970; Aug 04, 1971*; Dec 20, 1971; Jan 22, 1972*; Apr 26, 1972*; mentioned in letter dated Feb 18, 1976; also see International Museum of Photography; also see White, Minor
East Shoreline Charter Service: May 04, 1968
Eastwood, Alice: see Printed Material
Eckbo, Royston and Williams: Feb 10, 1947 (including notes and blueprints for landscaping Cunningham's yard in Green Street); Jun 09, 1947*; Sep 21, 1947*
Ecko, Evans: Apr 10, 1976
Edison Street Gallery: Mar 03, 1975; Apr 04, 1975*
Edwal Scientific Products Corp.: Mar 14, 1961*
Edwards, Norman: Aug 08, 1962*; Sep 20, 1962
Eitner, Lorenz: see Stanford University
Elkus, Jonathan, Marilyn and Ian: Dec 14, 1965*; May 1973
Ellegood, Donald: see Washington: University of Washington Press
Elliot, Ralph: Mar 21, 1962*
Embarcadero Center: Sep 20, 1972; Sep 29, 1972*
Emerson, Donna: undated (including a photograph of Emerson)
Emmons, Donn: Nov 12, 1974
Encyclopaedia Britannica: Jun 04, 1965; Jun 15, 1965*; Mar 17, 1971; Mar 22, 1971*; Apr 06, 1971; Apr 16, 1971*; Nov 10, 1971; Nov 23, 1971*; Jan 14, 1972; Jan 21, 1972*; Jan 25, 1972; Jan 28, 1972*; Feb 02, 1971; Feb 10, 1972; Feb 19, 1972*
English, Christopher: Jul 06, 1973; Jul 13, 1973*
Eng-Skell Company: Jan 05, 1959
Epstein, Ellen: Jan 09, 1968*
Epstein, Mrs. Jacob: Nov 21, 1963*
Erceg, Don and Jo (Joseph): Mar 01, 1965; Oct 18, 1965; Jun 21, 1966*; Sep 20, [1966]; Sep 26, 1966*; Nov 09, 1966*; Nov 13, 1966; Nov 25, 1966*; Jan 06, 1967; Jan 25, 1967*; Jun 21, 1967*; Jul 04, 1967; Jul 19, 1967*; Nov 07, 1967; Jul 05, 1968*; Jan 24, 1970*; May 03, 1971*; also see Lynch: Douglas Lynch Associates
Erpen, Gustave: Feb 06, 1966*
Esalen Institute: Apr 20, 1964; Apr 23, 1964*
Ets-Hokins, Jeremy: Sep 18, 1974*
Everyday Art Quarterly: Feb 13, 1948
Exchange National Bank of Chicago: Jan 24, 1968
f/64, Group: Sep 07, 1972 (booklet “The Group f/64 Controversy" by George M. Craven enclosed in letter from University of California at Berkeley)
Faber and Faber, Ltd.: Jan 26, 1970; Jan 31, 1970* (2); Feb 17, 1970
Falkner von Sonnenburg, Erwin: undated (in German); Jan 03, 1955 (in German); Aug 28, 1967*; Sep 23, 1968 (in German); Oct 19, 1968*; Dec 15, 1968*; Jan 12, 1969*; Jan 28, 1969 (in German); Feb 04, 1969*; Mar 11, 1969 (in German); Apr 16, 1969 (in German); Apr 23, 1969; Nov 28, 1970*; Jun 23, 1971*; Dec 13, 1971 (in German); Dec 25, 1971*; Apr 07, 1972 (in German); Feb 14, 1973 (in German); Jul 26, 1973*; Aug 21, 1973 (in German); Aug 01, 1974 (in German)
Falkner von Sonnenburg, Helene: May 1952 (in German); Jul 10, 1952; Aug 07, 1952; Sep 14, 1952*; Oct 15, 1952*; Nov 10, 1952*; Jan 05, 1953*; Jan 19, 1953*; Jan 27, 1953; Feb 02, 1953*; Feb 09, 1953*; Feb 25, 1953*; Apr 10, 1953*; May 19, 1953*; Jul 10, 1953*; Aug 20, 1953*; Oct 15, 1953 (death notice); mentioned in letters dated Dec 01, 1953*; Mar 19, 1954; May 14, 1954; May 24, 1954
The Family Circle: May 27, 1954*; Jun 07, 1954*; Jun 11, 1954; Jul 21, 1954; Jul 24, 1954*; Jan 25, 1955*; Jan 31, 1955; Jul 19, 1955; Jul 29, 1955; Aug 10, 1955; Sep 12, 1955*
Farley, Mr. and Mrs. William: Sep 22, 1948
Fascioni, Anna: Mar 23, 1971
Feininger, Andreas: Sep 19, 1937
Feininger, Lyonel and Julia: mentioned in [undated] letter from unidentified correspondent; Dec 14, 1951*; Feb 12, 1952*; Mar 18, 1952 (2); Mar 20, 1960
Feminist History Research Project: Jan 03, 1973
Fenno, J. (Jake?): May 27, 1968; May 30, 1968*
Ferry, Frances: Jan 30, 1966; [Mar 1969]; Apr 14, 1969*; Apr 19, 1969*; Jun 22, 1969*; Jul 11, 1969*; Sep 02, 1971*; Oct 16, 1975
Film Dynamics: May 21, 1973*
Finley, Mr. and Mrs. R. W.: Mar 31, 1975*
Finnegan, Josephine: Jul 05, 1972*; Jul 09, 1972
Fisher, Lois: mentioned in letter dated Mar 10, 1955
Focus Gallery: Nov 16, 1966; May 13, 1970; May 18, 1970*; May 30, 1970 (receipt for works); Apr 30, 1973; May 16, 1973; May 21, 1974; Apr 19, 1975; Jun 26, 1979; Jun 03, 1980
Foisie, Omer: see Dresden, Maud
Folger, Mr.: Feb 24, 1966*
Forbes, John D.: Jun 14, 1967*; Jun 17, 1967
Ford, Mr.: Nov 27, 1967*; May 21, 1968*
Forth, Robert: Jan 18, 1973*
Fortune: Mar 27, 1946
Fort Worth Art Center: Feb 27, 1956
Foster, Eve: Nov 13, 1957*; May 17, 1959*; Jan 18, 1960; Dec 10, 1960*
Foster (Zlatovski), Jane: undated; Oct 30, 1952; Dec 19, 1956; Jul 09, 1957* (including clippings about her indictment); see Notes for Foster's excerpts from My Ten Years as a Counterspy by Boris Morros, 1959
Foster, W. E.: Aug 14, 1957 (including clippings about Jane and George Foster's indictments)
FR Corporation: Feb 09, 1960
Franke & Heidecke: Apr 13, 1959; Jun 05, 1959*; Jun 18, 1959
Frankel, Peg: undated; Nov 28, 1983
Frankenstein, Alfred: see San Francisco Chronicle
Freed, Arthur: Aug 17, 1970
Freehe, Clifford: photograph of Freehe contained in letter from Dick Muffley dated May 19, 1974; also see Washington: University of Washington, Seattle
Freemesser, Bernard: Apr 09, 1969; Sep 24, 1973; Oct 27, 1973*; also see Oregon: University of Oregon
Friedman, Marian: [Apr 11, 1976]; May 07, 1976*
Friedman, Mickey: Apr 03, 1975; Jan 12, 1976; Jan 21, 1976; Mar 17, 1976*; Sep 22, 1976 (letter of condolence to Gryffyd Partridge)
Friends of Photography (gallery): Oct 12, 1971*; [May 31, 1973]; Jun 19, 1973; Feb 02, 1974*; May 14, 1974
Friends of the San Francisco Public Library: see San Francisco Public Library
Fuller, Pat: Apr 27, 1974; May 05, 1974*
Fuller, R. Buckminster: Mar 31, 1965
G., P. K.: Jul 05, 1968*
Gaelen, Leslie H.: May 16, 1961*; Nov 21, 1969; Nov 26, 1969*; Apr 29, 1970; Mar 20, 1971; Mar 26, 1971; Mar 31, 1971; May 11, 1971*; May 14, 1971*; Mun 03, 1971; Jun 09, 1971*
Galen, William: Mar 04, 1965; Aug 16, 1965
Gardner, Chrissie: Feb 18, 1968*; Aug 18, 1974*
Gardner, Juanita: Oct 16, 1972
Garnett, William: Dec 04, 1969*; May 09, 1970
Garrod, Richard: Feb 25, 1971
GAUSE (Western Managers of World Personalities): Mar 10, 1955; Mar 13, 1955*
Geddes, Norman Bel: Jun 27, 1932; Jul 07, 1932
Geen, Elizabeth: Mar 30, 1969*
Geldermann, Jessie and Arturo: Jun 12, 1958; Feb 02, 1959*; Feb 06, 1966*
General Foods Corp.: Nov 08, 1966*
Geske, Norman: see Nebraska: University of Nebraska
Gibbons, Mrs.: Jan 13, 1969*
Gichner, Lawrence: May 14, 1970; May 27, 1970*; Sep 14, 1970*
Gilbert, Arnold: Dec 02, 1969; Dec 15, 1969*; Dec 22, 1969; Feb 10, 1970*; Feb 16, 1970; Feb 19, 1970*
Gilbert, Jeffrey: Feb 05, 1976
Gill, Anne and Elwood: Oct 15, 1968; Oct 19, 1968*
Gillet, Anne: Feb 25, 1976 (including a term paper about Cunningham and 2 photographs of details on Cunningham's house)
Gilpin, Laura: May 31, 1959; Jun 04, 1959*; Feb 21, 1976*; Apr 17, 1976
Gisbon, Helen: Jan 28, 1958*
Glaezer, Rabbi: Oct 30, 1966
Glaser, Leslie: Jul 09, 1974*
Glenn: Jack Glenn Gallery: Mar 25, 1974; Apr 05, 1974; May 02, 1974; May 08, 1974*; May 09, 1974; Aug 23, 1974; Oct 04, 1974*
Golden Gate Magazine: May 08, 1961
Goldschmidt, Lisa: [Feb 07, 1969]; Feb 07, 1969*
Goldsmith, David: Jan 22, 1974*; Jan 19, 1975
Goldsmith, John: Oct 17, 1974
Goldsmith, T.: Nov 21, 1973
Goldstein, Virginia (Vagadu Aurelius' mother): Feb 07, 1971; Feb 27, 1971*
Goldstine, Daniel: Jul 05, 1964*
Goldstine, Edgar N.: undated; Jul 10, 1976 (letter of condolence to Gryffyd Partridge)
Goodger-Hill, G.: see Writings
Goodhue, Dr.: Sep 04, 1959* (2); Dec 07, 1972*
Goodwin, Betty: Nov 01, 1974
Goodwin, David: Dec 25, 1969 (photo Christmas card); Jul 22, 1970*; Jun 03, 1970; Dec 25, 1973; Apr 11, 1976
Gordon, Richard: Oct 11, 1974
Gorsline, Jerry: Sep 03, 1968
Grady, Jim: Nov 26, 1956*
Graham: Martha Graham Dance Co.: Apr 29, 1976*
Grant, Cary: Oct 24, 1970*
Grant, Verne: undated; Oct 24, [1974]; Nov 20, 1974
Graves, Morris: Apr 13, 1969*; Feb 23, 1972*; Jun 11, 1973*; Jun 30, 1973; Jul 05, 1973*; Jul 30, 1973; Aug 17, 1973*; Sep 03, 1973*; Dec 21, 1973
Graves, Wallace: Nov 12, 1972
Gray, Burt: Oct 11, 1974*
Grey, Abby and Benjamin: Jan 24, 1965; Feb 10, 1965*
Grieve, Ginger: Feb 04, 1976 (including a photograph of Grieve)
Grotch, Stanley: Nov 16, 1971*; Jan 08, 1971*
Grover, Oliver D.: Jun 26, 1912
Grubb, Erica: see Washington: University of Washington Press
Guggenheim: John Simon Guggenheim Memorial Foundation: undated* (2; one re Gini Dodge Leonard); Nov 30, 1956* (re Ruth Asawa Lanier); Nov 03, 1959 (recommendation for Cunningham from Theodore Roethke); Nov 16, 1959*; Feb 10, 1960; Nov 22, 1966; Dec 21, 1966* (re Thomas Knight); Jan 30, 1967*; Nov 22, 1967; Dec 07, 1968*; Aug 28, 1969; Sep 15, 1969*; Feb 20, 1970; Mar 20, 1970 (2); Mar 23, 1970 (telegram awarding fellowship); Apr 02, 1970; Apr 04, 1970*; Apr 08, 1970; Apr 09, 1970; Apr 21, 1970 (2); Apr 27, 1970 (2); Apr 30, 1970*; May 14, 1970; Jun 01, 1970*; Jun 08, 1970; Jul 26, 1970*; Jul 29, 1970; Sep 11, 1970; Oct 28, 1970*; Nov 18, 1970*; Dec 04, 1970; Dec 11, 1970; Dec 18, 1970*; Dec 22, 1970; Jan 11, 1971*; Jan 15, 1971; Jan 27, 1971; Jan 30, 1971*; Feb 22, 1971*; Mar 03, 1971; Mar 07, 1971*; Mar 11, 1971; Mar 14, 1971*; Apr 07, 1971; Apr 26, 1971; May 02, 1971*; May 11, 1971; Aug 04, 1971*; Aug 06, 1971; Aug 13, 1971; Dec 02, 1971*; Dec 06, 1971; Dec 09, 1971; Dec 25, 1971*; Feb 24, 1972; Feb 29, 1972*; Jun 10, 1972*; Jun 13, 1972; Nov 21, 1972; Dec 01, 1972* (including recommendations by Cunningham for Bill Heick and Walter Chappel); May 03, 1973*; Oct 30, 1974*; Nov 20, 1974; Dec 04, 1974* (letter of recommendation for Judy Dater); Dec 10, 1974
Guillumette: Paul Guillumette, Inc.: Jul 17, 1953
Gustafson, Egil: mentioned in letter dated Nov 02, 1974
Gustaitis, Rasa (Rasa Gustaitis Moss): Dec 24, 1969
Gustin, Paul and Ina: Aug 19, 1965*; Oct 07, 1965
Guthrie, Helen: see MacDonald, Dorothy and Helen
Gutman, Judith Mara: Apr 25, 1971
Haberstitch, David: see Smithsonian Institution; see Writings
Hader, Berta and Elmer: undated; Jul 10, 1956; Aug 22, 1956; Sep 11, 1965*; Jul 22, 1968*; May 01, 1969; Dec 28, 1969; Apr 20, 1971*; Jun 21, 1973; mentioned in letter Oct 19, 1973*; Feb 21, 1974*; Feb 25, 1974; Feb 25, 1975*
Hagan, R. A.: Apr 12, 1975 (poem by Hagan)
Hagberg, Jochen: see Writings
Hagel, Hansel, and Otto: Feb 24, 1965; Apr 22, 1968*; Oct 26, 1973
Hagen, Charles: see Afterimage
Hall, James Baker: Mar 14, 1976
Hall, Norman: Dec 09, 1960*,Dec 17, 1960; May 12, 1961; Oct 07, 1962*; May 05, 1963*; Nov 21, 1963*; Dec 30, 1963; Feb 22, 1964*; Jun 11, 1965*; Sep 22, 1968*; Oct 07, 1968; Oct 11, 1968*; Jul 22, 1969*; Nov 25, 1969*; also see London Times; also see Photography
Halprin, Ann: Nov 1970
Hammid, Hella: Apr 25, 1964*; Jan 22, 1967*; Oct 07, 1968*; Aug 27, 1969*; Apr 25, 1972 (letter of recommendation)
Handbook Co.: Mar 28, 1972*
Hansen family: Dec 25, 1968 (including photograph)
Harcourt Brace Jovanovich, Inc.: Feb 07, 1973; Feb 14, 1973; Feb 18, 1973*
Harmon family: Dec 25, 1962
Harnden, Betsey: Jan 20, 1973*
Harootian, Koren Der: Dec 28, 1956
Harper's Bazaar: Jan 07, 1963*; Nov 07, 1970*; Jan 1971 (2)
Harrington, La Mar: see Henry Gallery
Harris, Eugenia: May 11, 1975*
Harrison, Halstead: undated
Harrison, Lynne: Oct 27, 1965; Nov 02, 1965*; Dec 26, 1965; Apr 05, 1966; Oct 16, 1966; Nov 03, 1966*; Mar 08, 1967*; Mar 25, 1967; Feb 08, 1968; Feb 11, 1968*; Aug 09, 1968*; Oct 05, 1973; Jan 23, 1974; Mar 27, 1974*; Apr 23, 1974*; Sep 30, 1974; Oct 02, 1974*
Hartman, Louis: Dec 29, 1967*
Hauberg, John: Mar 28, 1972; Apr 17, 1972*
Haupt, Hanna: Feb 09, 1961 (in German)
Haupt, Peter and Dorle: Jan 25, 1959*; Nov 29, 1960*; Sep 07, 1961 (in German); Dec 14, 1965*; Jul 27, 1967; Aug 28, 1967*; Jul 06, 1968*; Sep 23, 1968*; Nov 24, 1968; Dec 08, 1968*; Jan 10, 1969; Aug 29, 1969*; Jan 03, 1969; May 24, 1971*; Sep 16, 1972; Oct 04, 1972; Jun 09, 1973; Oct 06, 1973; Dec 03, 1974*
Haupt, Otto: Aug 08, 1960 (in German)
Haven, Tom: [Jul 25, 1973]; Jul 25, 1973*
Haynes, Bruce and Joan (Partridge): Aug 30, 1967; Sep 26, 1967*; Dec 29, 1967*; Jan 17, 1968; Jan 31, 1968; Apr 04, 1968*; Jan 05, 1969*; Feb 02, 1969; Feb 05, 1969*; Apr 13, 1969*; Feb 29, 1972*; Jun 07, 1974*; Nov 18, 1974*
Healey, Myrtle: undated calling card
Heick, Bill: undated; mentioned in letter dated Dec 01, 1972*
Heick, Helen: Oct 09, 1958 (including a typescript of Heick's “On a Freighter to Japan" and a reprint of her "A Panacea Called Haramaki"); Dec 16, 1960*
Heinecken, Robert: see California: University of California at Los Angeles
Heino, Vivica: Mar 25, 1971*; May 05, 1972*
Hellman, Lillian: Dec 02, 1973*; Dec 26, 1973
Helps, Bob: [Jan 31, 1974]; Jan 31, 1974*
Henod Textiles: undated